

- AHMEDABAD INDIA 380018
- +91 8320622733
- rekhabadriprasad13@gmail.com

## SUMMARY

Analytical Junior Accountant with 2.5 years of experience working in SAP FICO settings. Expertly maintaining detailed for reporting, ensuring complete accuracy. Meticulous attention to detail with outstanding written and verbal communication skills. Detailed Junior Accountant with 2+ years of accounts experience. Highly skilled in performing accurate balance sheet reconciliations. Indepth SAP knowledge, producing accurate payments reports within 5-10-minute timeframe. Experienced in day-to-day accounting processes and applicable regulations. Dedicated to maintaining accurate records with attention to detail and expert financial knowledge.

### SKILLS

- Concise communicator
- In-depth SAP knowledge
- Excellent mathematics skills
- import-export sipping data analysis
- Full-cycle accounting
- Payment processing
- A/P and A/R reconciliations
- Financial account management
- Account reconciliation

# REKHA MAHAVAR

#### **EXPERIENCE**

February 2021 - June 2023

Junior Accountant belfrost international LLP | ahmedabad, india

- Used SAP accounting software to perform bookeeping, invoicing and bank reconciliations.
- Posted accounts receivable payments made by cash, cheque or credit card payments.
- Created and maintained journal entries, maintaining exceptional accuracy throughout.
- Kept communications regular with internal and external customers, updating them on matters including timeframes and order status.
- Closely monitored and collected shipment statistics for in and outbound flows of materials, parts and goods for purposes.
- Ensured supplies, stock, materials, packages and products were processed through the delivery systems efficiently and safely.

July 2020 - January 2021

HR Recruiter our globle connect pvt ltd | ahmedabad, india

- Managed candidate hiring processes, from shortlisting candidates to hiring and onboarding.
- Researched ideal candidates using range of platforms, including LinkedIn, social media and CV database tools.
- Conducted extensive analysis into candidate CVs, searching for keywords and specific skills to streamline shortlisting.

January 2020 - June 2020

Telecom Executive Just Dial | Ahmedabad, India

- · Identified, addressed and either resolved or escalated project issues.
- Reported regularly on project data and kept leadership informed of progress.
- · Analysed and adapted workflows to meet evolving needs.

#### **EDUCATION**

2023

Master of Business Administration | finance

R B INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT GUJRAT TECHNOLOGY , Ahmedabad. GJ

MBA Graduate

#### LANGUAGES

English, Gujarati, Hindi: First Language

Gujarati: C2 Hindi: C2

Proficient Proficient

English: C1

Advanced